$  Active in Inventory	  Active in Inventory
$  Active in World	  Active in World
$Add to List	Add to List
$Blacklists	Blacklists
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_ADD_HOTKEY	Tap to add the selected item to the currently active list.\nIn the inventory menu, select an item by highlighting it. In the world, select an item by focusing on it.
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_ADD_HOTKEY_IN_INVENTORY	Enables the add hotkey in the inventory menu.\nWhen enabled, highlight items in the inventory menu and tap the add hotkey to add them to the active filter list.
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_ADD_HOTKEY_IN_WORLD	Enables the add hotkey in the world.\nWhen enabled, focus on items in the world and tap the add hotkey to add them to the active filter list.
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_DEBUG_LEVEL	Enable logging of DeActivator debug messages to your Papyrus log.\nOff: Initialization notifications only. Debug: Normal debug notifications.\nTrace: Extremely verbose debug notifications. These will fill up your Papyrus log.
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_REMOVE_HOTKEY	Tap to remove the selected item from the currently active list.\nIn the inventory menu, select an item by highlighting it. In the world, select an item by focusing on it.
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_REMOVE_HOTKEY_IN_INVENTORY	Enables the remove hotkey in the inventory menu.\nWhen enabled, highlight items in the inventory menu and tap the remove hotkey to remove them from the active filter list.
$DEACTIVATOR_HIGHLIGHT_REMOVE_HOTKEY_IN_WORLD	Enables the remove hotkey in the world.\nWhen enabled, focus on items in the world and tap the remove hotkey to remove them from the active filter list.
$DEACTIVATOR_KEY_CONFLICT_{}_FROM_SKYRIM	This key is already mapped to {} from Skyrim.\nAre you sure you want to continue?
$DEACTIVATOR_KEY_CONFLICT_{}_FROM_{}	This key is already mapped to {} from {}.\nAre you sure you want to continue?
$DEBUG	DEBUG
$Debug Logging Level	Debug Logging Level
$Debugging	Debugging
$Hotkeys	Hotkeys
$No	No
$OFF	OFF
$Remove from List	Remove from List
$Settings	Settings
$TRACE	TRACE
$Whitelists	Whitelists
$Yes	Yes